It's raining.
But I'll try my best, even in the rain!
I'll get more candy!
That was close.
Dobato!
It's your fault I'm all muddy!
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... Gift of the rain.
It's okay if you're muddy, Ioryogi.
The rain will wash it right off.
No it's not! Then I'll be soaked!
Kobato.
Good morning!
Miss Sayaka!
Um... Miss Sayaka?
What?
Where are we going?
To your place.
Here we are.
Can I really live here?
Yeah, if you'd like.
Let's go in.
Okay!
Let me introduce you. This is Chitose, my friend and the manager of these apartments.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Hanato Kobato.
Kobato, huh. Good to meet you, I'm Mihara Chitose.
If there's anything you don't know or have trouble with, feel free to ask.
Okay!
Chitose, you take care of the rest.
Later, Kobato.
I'm going back to the nursery.
Okay!
Thanks a ton!
I'll come help out later.
Sayaka always worries so much about other people.
Kobato.
Yes!
I'm glad to meet you.
She seems so kind.
We'll be leeching here for now, huh.
I'm Hanato Kobato! I'll be helping out here from today on!
You're not the one helping out.
So, when will your things arrive?
Umm...
This is it!
What about your mattress and stuff?
I don't have one!
Oh my...
All right, let me show you around then.
Okay.
What a wonderful building this is.
Thanks.
This is a wonderful room, Ioryogi.
Ioryogi?
Huh? Huhhhh?
Where'd he go?
Dobato...
You left me behind again!
Didn't I tell you!? I'm a stuffed animal here!
I'm sorry!
Come on...
Hey!
All right...
The nursery class is starting.
That's right!
If I don't hurry, I'll be late!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?
I'm fine. But what about him?
Sorry, he's all muddy now.
He's so cute!
All right, nice and clean.
Here ya go. See ya.
Thank you!
Welp, she's got more sense than you do.
Kobato, what did you think of your room?
Oh, it's wonderful having a roof I can relax under.
Oh, that's nice.
Kobato!
Let's play!
I'm cleaning now.
Then I'll help out!
Us too!
Thanks!
What should I do?
Well-
How about me?
Why did you even have to set her up with an apartment?
Well, everyone's so happy now that she's here.
Don't tease her.
How many times do you plan on getting hurt like that?
You're right.
Right now, we have to be on our guard against anyone.
I'm glad it's stopped raining.
There's no class at the nursery today, so I can go collect more candy!
Man, it was sunny up until now.
I told you to bring an umbrella.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't look like it's gonna stop soon.
We're just gonna have to get soaked.
Why does it have to be just me?
Don't you have an umbrella?
Nope...
Here you go.
Go ahead and use it.
But...
Go ahead, I keep it around for customers.
I'll bring it back when it stops raining!
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Thanks a lot!
That was pretty up-front for you.
All right, just like that.
Okay!
I'll collect information on people that want to be healed here!
I guess that works.
People keep coming and going here.
I'll try my best!
I didn't find anything out.
What's wrong?
The umbrella I borrowed is gone!
What?
Did someone take the wrong one?
They probably just walked off with it.
Can people just go and do that?
No way!
Oh man... And I had borrowed it from the baker...
Huh?
It's you again.
It's you from yesterday.
What's up?
I lost my umbrella...
Here!
You can have mine.
But...
Go ahead!
I live right near here.
And he'll get all wet without one, too.
Tadokoro!
If you just keep buying and eating you're gonna get fat again.
Shut up! You're an idiot, Katsuragi!
Wait!
Um...
Thank you!
If you don't wait, I'm gonna smack you!
Wait!? You will even if I wait!
What!?
Katsuragi!
So there's people who would give up their umbrella even if it means they get wet...
Good morning!
Good morning, Kobato.
Huh?
You've got tatami marks on your cheek.
Later!
How embarassing! Having tatami marks on my cheek. Chitose must think I'm so weird.
Good morning!
Huh?
Thanks for the umbrella!
So you found my school.
Yeah. When I went to apologize to the baker I'd borrowed the umbrella from, he picked it out by your green uniform.
Ioryogi says thanks too.
Ioryogi?
Yeah!
Oh, you mean this stuffed animal?
What a funny name.
I'm called Hanato Kobato.
I'm Tadokoro Mutsumi.
Tadokoro!
Your hair's sticking up in back!
Shut up! I don't need you to tell me!
Where is it?
It's fine.
I had a tatami print on my cheek this morning.
I don't want to imitate that.
Sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, I've got morning practice, so-
By the way, that boy before was mean.
He's just like Fujimoto.
If I'm late, he'll be even meaner.
You're one minute and 23 seconds late.
One minute?
Even if it's one minute, you're still late.
I'm sorry.
It's because you slept in until the last minute.
The tatami print is going away.
You must've slipped off your mattress.
I don't have a mattress!
'Morning, Kobato.
Good morning.
Did Fujimoto say something to you?
Well, um...
He's a bit blunt, but he's not a bad guy.
But if he's mean to you any more, tell me.
I'll give him a good spanking!
Spanking?
Yeah, like the old days.
The old days?
Hey! It's finally sunny.
We can dry the nap blankets.
Yeah! I'll do that now!
Goodbye, Kobato!
Goodbye!
Looks like it's going to rain again.
Kobato, where's your umbrella?
I don't have one.
Fujimoto's still here, you can walk home with him.
I still have stuff to do. Just take my umbrella.
I don't want to share one with you anyway.
Sharing an umbrella?
Where you have two people under one umbrella.
Miss Sayaka was right.
It really is raining.
The person who took it by accident brought it back.
Huh? Kobato?
You again?
Tadokoro Mutsumi!
Just call me Mutsumi. What's up?
The umbrella came back!
I see. That's great.
Yeah! Shopping again, Mutsumi?
Yeah, kendo team practice is so tough I'm starving by the end of it.
You seem like you're trying hard.
But...
If I eat too much, I'll get fat.
Here, have these.
Can I?
Sure, go ahead.
All right! Later!
So that's sharing an umbrella.
Mutsumi!
Mutsumi looked so sad.
I wonder how I could cheer her up.
I dunno. Maybe more of these.
Good evening.
Open up!
Hello!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Sorry about the racket.
Pleased to meet you. I'm the manager's daughter, Chiho.
I'm Chise.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Hanato Kobato.
You don't have a mattress, do you?
Right.
Mama said you could use this.
Are you sure?
Well, it's used.
Anyway, see you later!
Thanks a lot!
They gave me a mattress.
You're not the one that's supposed to be getting healed!
Oh, that's right.
I'm supposed to be making Mutsumi happy again.
But how?
I don't know, but I'll try my best!
Hey! What are you gonna do?
I think it's best to leave her alone for now.
Excuse me!
I'd like to talk with you!
About Mutsumi!
Please!
What do you mean?
Well... I'd like you to share an umbrella with Mutsumi!
Please!
Why with her?
What's wrong with it?
Mutsumi
What's all this about?
Lately, you've looked so sad...
When you shared an umbrella with other girls.
I don't really...
Then why?
Well...
Sorry if I'm overdoing it.
I just want Mutsumi to be happy.
So...
Here!
Please share an umbrella with Mutsumi!
Kobato?
Please!
Isn't that being mean to the new girl?
Get under it.
What? I told you, I'm fine!
I'm not going out with that other girl.
I just walked with her because she forgot her umbrella.
There you go, Mutsumi.
Hurry up. Let's go!
Katsuragi!
Hold on! I'm getting wet!
Back off.
Quit complaining.
It's too cramped!
You're...
But it really is!
Complain all you want, it's still a small umbrella.
Mutsumi doesn't look too happy.
They're fine like that.
Really?
It's funny, Ioryogi.
What is?
I'm getting more candy.
That's why you healed that girl, right?
I just helped out because I wanted her to cheer up.
No matter what you were trying to do, you healed her scarred heart.
Really?
Getting more candy is the best proof of that.
That's great!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
What's this atmosphere?
What is it, Kohaku?
Oh, it's nothing, Shuichiro.
Let's go.
You somehow got it right this time, so you can have a good score.
Really!?
Are you okay, Ioryogi!?
Dobato!
Zero points!
That's so mean, Ioryogi! You said I scored well!
It's your fault that I'm covered in mud and ink!
It's okay if you're muddy! The rain will wash it right off!
The rain won't wash away my rage!
No way!
People all want to fly
but they're cheated by gravity
everyone can really fly
She must be so unhappy because
she forgot her own shadow somewhere
Then...
If you tell me "thanks", if you say "thanks" and smile
Going back and forth, we'll be happy
You'll be happy, there'll be nothing to worry about
As long as we're together
It's strange, I'm crying even though I'm happy
... Pulsing leaves.
Next episode